A Guide to the Christian de Duve papers, Rockefeller University Faculty, Accession 2009:084 FA934
Rockefeller Archive Center
Christian de Duve papers, Rockefeller University Faculty, Accession 2009:084
1927-2005
Rockefeller Archive Center
De Duve, Christian
Rockefeller University
FA934
99.56 Cubic Feet 76 record storage boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged materials are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
Scope and Contents
The Christian de Duve papers are comprised of: workshop, conference, symposium, and meeting records; lecture files; administrative files; correspondence; reprints, papers, dissertations, manuscripts, and other publications.
- Extinct Commitments, 1962-1964 (Box 1)
- Miles Meeting, 1962 May (Box 1)
- U.N.E.S.C.O. Symposium at the University of Buffalo, 1962 October 22-27 (Box 1)
- Stratford-on-Avon Meeting, 1962 September 2-12 (Box 1)
- CIBA Meeting, 1963 February 12-14 (Box 1)
- ICRO Meeting, New York, 1963 (Box 1)
- Biochemistry Society, Louvain (Box 1)
- Bernard, Claude, Montreal, 1963 March (Box 1)
- Embryology Course, Meeting, Naples, 1963 October 3-5 (Box 1)
- Harvey Lecture, Gutman/Mount Sinai, 1963 November 21 (Box 1)
- Arthritis Foundation, Boston, 1963 December (Box 1)
- 6th International Congress of Biochemistry, 1964 July 26-August 1 (Box 1)
- Symposium Vesale, 1964 October 22 (Box 1)
- Extinct Commitments, 1965 (Box 1)
- Santiago, 1964 October (Box 1)
- Symposium Biophysics Physiology Of Biology Transport, 1965 June 14-17 (Box 1)
- Paris Meeting, 1965 September (Box 1)
- Symposium, Giessen, Germany, 1965 October 14-16 (Box 1)
- Symposium on Insulin, Brookhaven, New York, 1965 November 8-10 (Box 1)
- Symposium on Subcellular Movement, 1965 November 10-12 (Box 1)
- Symposium Belges a Tokio (Box 1)
- Extinct Commitments, 1966 (Box 1)
- Chicago, 1966 March 14 (Box 1)
- Harvard (Box 1)
- Gordon Research Conference (Box 1)
- Congress of Hematology, Australia, 1966 August 21-29 (Box 1)
- Japan Symposium, 1966 (Box 1)
- American Society for Cell Biology, 6th Meeting, Houston, Texas, 1966 November 17-19 (Box 1)
- Laboratory Visit and Talk, Rockefeller University (RU), 1966 November 9 (Box 1)
- Freiburg Symposium (Box 1)
- Extinct Commitments, 1967 (Box 1)
- Michigan, 1967 October 18-20 (Box 1)
- Montreal, 1967 October 24-26 (Box 1)
- London Meeting on Drugs, 1967 (Box 1)
- 15th Annual Colloquium, Brugge, Bel., "Protides of the Biological Fluids", 1967 May 3-7 (Box 1)
- Federation Meeting, 1967 April 17-22 (Box 1)
- Lecture, Amsterdam, 1967 January 6 (Box 1)
- 7th Annual Meeting, American Society for Cell Biology, 1967 November 13-15 (Box 1)
- Vanderbilt University (Box 1)
- International Congress of Biochemistry, Tokyo, 1967 (Box 1)
- Extinct Commitments, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
- New York Academy of Sciences, 1968 November 14-16 (Box 1)
- New York Heart Association, Symposium on Membrane Proteins (Box 1)
- Andover, New Hampshire, 1968 (Box 1)
- UCLA (University of California Los Angeles) Seminar, 1968 June 27 (Box 1)
- University of Washington Lecture (Box 1)
- Royal Society Symposium, 1968 June 20 (Box 1)
- Brookhaven (Box 1)
- Brandeis, 1968 May 8 (Box 1)
- Chicago, University of Chicago, 1968 March 20 (Box 1)
- SUNY at Buffalo, Talk, 1968 March 19 (Box 1)
- Reims, Biologie Cellulaire, 1969 March 27-29 (Box 1)
- Microsomes Symposium, Bethesda, Maryland, 1968 February 16-17 (Box 1)
- Gordon Conference, Meriden, New Hampshire, 1967 July 3-7 (Box 2)
- Applications and New Invitations (Box 2)
- Parks, Correspondence (Box 2)
- Correspondence, Speakers, General Information (Box 2)
- Budget (Box 2)
- Programs (Box 2)
- Extinct Commitments, 1968 (Box 2)
- American Society for Cell Biology, 1968 November 11-13 (Box 2)
- Tehran (Box 2)
- XII International Congress of Cell Biology, Brussels, 1968 August 25-31 (Box 2)
- Extinct Commitments, 1969 (Box 2)
- Université de Sherbrooke, 1969 June 19 (Box 2)
- New York Academy of Sciences, 1969 May 27 (Box 2)
- New York Academy of Sciences, 1969 May (Box 2)
- University of California, San Francisco Medical Center, 1969 April 30 (Box 2)
- The American Society of Biological Chemistry, Atlantic City, NJ, 1969 April 13-16 (Box 2)
- Rutgers University, 1969 March 20 (Box 2)
- Seminar, Harvard Medical School, 1969 March 12 (Box 2)
- University of London, 1969 February 12-13 (Box 2)
- Seminar, University of Illinois (Box 2)
- Bio-Pap Symposia, Miami, Florida, 1969 January (Box 2)
- Gordon Conference, 1969 (Box 2)
- 1969 (Box 2)
- Summer Course on Aging, Public Health Service, National Institute of Health (NIH) (Box 2)
- Extinct Commitments, 1969 July-December (Box 2)
- University of Connecticut, Lecture on Lysosomes, 1969 December 15 (Box 2)
- Harvard University, Seminar of Peroxisome, 1969 December 5 (Box 2)
- American Society for Cell Biology, Detroit, 1969 November 6-8 (Box 2)
- Sloan-Kettering Lecture, 1969 October 23 (Box 2)
- University of Torino, 1969 October 14 (Box 2)
- Rocky Mountain Section, Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine, 1969 October 11 (Box 2)
- Kingsbrook Jewish Medical Center, Basic Science Series, 1969 October 1 (Box 2)
- European Association Study of Diabetes, Montpellier, 1969 September 15 (Box 2)
- Leiden: Mononuclear Phagocytes, 1969 September 2-5 (Box 2)
- University of Tubingen, 1969 July 20-22 (Box 2)
- University of Surrey, London, Workshop Course on Zonal Centrifugation, 1969 July 14-21 (Box 2)
- International Symposium on Cell Biology and Cytopharmacology, 1969 July 7-11 (Box 2)
- Extinct Commitments, 1970 January-April 28 (Box 2)
- Physiologisch, Chemisches Institut der Georg, August Universitat Gottingen (Germany), Seminar, 1970 April 28 (Box 2)
- Medizinische Hochschule Hannover, Seminar, Hannover, Germany, 1970 April 28 (Box 2)
- European Society for Clinical Investigation, Guest Lecture, Holland, 1970 April 25 (Box 2)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) Lecture (Seminar), 1970 April 22 (Box 2)
- Dartmouth Medical School Seminar, Hanover, New Hampshire, 1970 March 10 (Box 2)
- University of California, Irvine, Lecture, 1970 March 6 (Box 2)
- New York University (NYU), Skin and Cancer Unit, Lecture on Lysosomes, 1970 March 5 (Box 2)
- Columbia University Colloquium, 1970 February 27 (Box 2)
- Seminar, Lysosomes et Granulations Specifiques, Paris, 1970 January 22 (Box 2)
- Extinct Commitments, 1970 April 29-May (Box 2)
- University of Chicago, Departments of Medicine and Pediatrics Lecture, 1970 May 27 (Box 2)
- Stony Brook State University, Talk of Peroxisomes, 1970 May 14 (Box 2)
- "Biochemische Analytik", Munich, Talk, 1970 April 30 (Box 2)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) Preservation Conference, "Self-Destruct Mechanisms", Washington, D. C., 1970 April 23 (Box 2)
- Dresden, East Germany Visit, M. von Ardenne, Forschungsinstitut, 1970 April (Box 2)
- Extinct Commitments, 1970 July-August (Box 3)
- Wenner-Gren Symposium, 1970 August 23-27 (Box 3)
- NATO Advanced Study Institute, Course, Md-Donk, 1970 August 16-29 (Box 3)
- 2nd Summer Course of Aging, Stanford University, 1970 July 6-17 (Box 3)
- Extinct Commitments, 1970 June-August (Box 3)
- University of Leiden, 1970 June 26 (Box 3)
- Extinct Commitments, 1970 September-December (Box 3)
- Tenth Annual Meeting of the American Society for Cell Biology, 1970 November 19-21 (Box 3)
- Voyages, 1970 (Box 3)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), Neurosciences Research Program Meeting, Brookline, MA, 1970 December 14 (Box 3)
- Fordham University, Lecture, 1970 December 2 (Box 3)
- Université de Sherbrooke, 1970 October 24 (Box 3)
- University of Texas, Dallas, Lecture, 1970 November 23 (Box 3)
- University of Tennessee, Oak Ridge Graduate School Lecture (on Lysosomes), 1970 October 9 (Box 3)
- West Virginia University, Seminar, 1970 October 8 (Box 3)
- Réunion Européene de Chimie Therapeutiqe, 1970 September 14-17 (Box 3)
- European Group for the Study of Lysosomes, 1st International Research Conference, (Louvain), 1970 September 12-15 (Box 3)
- 8th international Congress of Biochemistry, Switzerland, 1970 September 3-9 (Box 3)
- Extinct Commitments, 1971 January-April (Box 3)
- XIXth Annual Colloquium, Protides of the Biological Fluids, Brugge, Belgium, 1971 April 28-May 2 (Box 3)
- University College Colloquium, Cardiff, Great Britain, and CIBA, London (Box 3)
- 3rd Symposium de Biochimie et de Nutrition, Tabriz, Iran, 1971 April 14-24 (Box 3)
- Washington State University (Pullman), and University of Washington, Seattle, 1971 April 5 and 8 (Box 3)
- Lecture, "Lysosomes in Pathology", Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons, 1971 April 2 (Box 3)
- Rockefeller University Trustee Dinner, 1971 January 27 (Box 3)
- Long Island University Seminar, 1971 January 18 (Box 3)
- Extinct Commitments, 1971 May-October (Box 3)
- Enzyme Club Talk, "Lysosomes and the Breakdown of Cell Constituents", 1971 October 19 (Box 3)
- Seminar, CIBA-GIEGY, Ardsley, New York, 1971 October 15 (Box 3)
- Seminar, Johns Hopkins University, 1971 October 12 (Box 3)
- EGSL International Research Conference, Yugoslavia, 1971 September 26-29 (Box 3)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) Summer Course on Aging, Bar Harbor, Maine, 1971 September 6-17 (Box 3)
- 8th Latin American Congress on Physiological Sciences, Caracas, Venezuela, 1971 July 12-17 (Box 3)
- Extinct Commitments, 1971 November-December (Box 3)
- Activities, 1971 (Box 3)
- Lecture, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tennessee, 1971 November 22-23 (Box 3)
- Extinct Commitments, 1971 November-December (Box 3)
- NIGMS (National Institute of General Medical Sciences) Advisory Council Seminar (National Institute of Health (NIH)), 1971 November 19 (Box 3)
- American Society for Cell Biology Meeting, New Orleans, 1971 November 17-20 (Box 3)
- Extinct Commitments, 1971 November-December (Box 3)
- NIH (National Institutes of Health), Consultation with Laster, Bethesda, 1971 November 10 (Box 3)
- Extinct Commitments, 1972 January-June (Box 3)
- Gordon Conference on Lysosomes, 1972 (Box 3)
- Académie Royale de Médicine de Belgique, Bruxelles, Belgique, 1972 June 24 (Box 3)
- Swiss Serum and Vaccine Institute Conference", Host Resistance to Diseases", 1972 June 20-22 (Box 3)
- "Slowing Down the Age Clock" Scientists Meeting, The Century Club, New York, 1972 June 8 (Box 3)
- Academie Pontificale des Sciences, Sesseion pleniere, 1972 April 10-16 (Box 3)
- Seminar on Rheumatoid Arthritis of the Upper Extremity, New York Society of the Relief of the Ruptured and Crippled, 1972 March 8 (Box 3)
- Seminar, Universiteit van Amsterdam, 1972 February 4 (Box 3)
- Radiodiffusion Television Belge (Danblon), 1971 July (Box 3)
- Extinct Commitments, General/Singapore/Bali/Hong Kong/Australia/New Zealand, 1972 (Box 4)
- Extinct Commitments: Kyoto/Inland Sea/Tokyo/Hakone, 1972 (Box 4)
- Tokyo/Hakone (Box 4)
- Kyoto/Inland Sea (Box 4)
- "Lysosomes and Perioxisomes" (Box 4)
- Extinct Commitments, 1972 July-December (Box 4)
- Conférences, Symposiums, Congrés, 1972 (Box 4)
- Lecture, New York University, Sabatini, 1972 December 15 (Box 4)
- Seminar, "Lysosomes and Disease", Institute for Muscle Disease, New York, New York, 1972 December 12 (Box 4)
- "Lysosomes and Disease: A New Look", Rockefeller University (RU) Research Colloquia, 1972 December 8 (Box 4)
- "Lysosomes in Cell Physiology and Pathology", Milton S. Hershey Medical Center, Hershey, Pennsylvania, 1972 December 7 (Box 4)
- Lecture-"Lysosomes" Mt. Sinai School of Medicine, New York, New York, 1972 November 30 (Box 4)
- Seminar, St. John's University, Jamaica, New York, 1972 November 15 (Box 4)
- Course, "Cellular and Molecular Aspects of Aging", Feb Research Institute, Temple University, 1972 November 29 (Box 4)
- Extinct Commitments, 1972 July-December (Box 4)
- American Society for Cell Biology, 12th Meeting, St. Louis, Missouri, 1972 November 8-11 (Box 4)
- Symposium, "Nouvelles Perspectives en Biologie Cellulaire", Ottawa, Canada Association Canadienne Francaise pour l' Advancement des Sciences, 1972 October 3 (Box 4)
- "Lysosomes and Aging", Cell Culture Procedures for Aging Research Course, The University of Vermont, Burlington, 1972 September 28 (Box 4)
- Extinct Commitments, 1972 July-December (Box 4)
- EGSL, 3rd International Research Conference, "Lysosomes in Cell Pathology", Louvain, Belgium, 1972 September 12-16 (Box 4)
- "Geneeskundige Dagen Van Antwerpen", Lecture, Antwerp, Belgium, 1972 September 14 (Box 4)
- Extinct Commitments, 1973 January-April (Box 4)
- Special Meeting of the Section for Natural Sciences, Royal Netherlands Academy of Arts and Sciences, Amsterdam, The Netherlands, 1973 April 28 (Box 4)
- Histochemical Society Meeting, Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1973 April 14-15 (Box 4)
- Buffalo, New York, Roswell Park Memorial Institute, Seminar and State University of New York at Buffalo, Seminar, 1973 April 5-6 (Box 4)
- FEBS (Federation of European Biochemical Societies) Special Meeting on Industrial Aspects of Biochemistry, Dublin, Ireland, 1973 April 15-19 (Box 4)
- Symposium on Investigative Techniques in Cell Pathology, Washington, D. C., 1973 March 3 (Box 4)
- "The Living Cell, New York University School of Continuing Education, 1973 February 14 (Box 4)
- La Chaire Francqui, Université de Liège, Belgium (Box 4)
- Extinct Commitments, 1973 May-June (Box 4)
- 2nd International Symposium, Electron Microscopy and Cytochemistry, Drienerio, The Netherlands, 1973 June 25-29 (Box 4)
- 2nd International Symposium on Cytopharmacology, Cytopharmacology of Secretion, Venice, Italy, 1973 June 17-22 (Box 4)
- Deuxieme centenaire de la Fondation de l'Acdemie Royale des Sciences Belgique, 1973 May 14-17 (Box 4)
- GDR Biochemical Society Symposium, "Intracellular Protein Catabolism", 1973 May 7-11 (Box 4)
- The Rockefeller University Council, Inaugural Meeting, 1973 June 11 (Box 4)
- Université de Umeå, Sweden, Echange de professeurs avec la Suede, 1973 June (Box 4)
- Extinct Commitments, 1973 July-September (Box 4)
- Merck and Company, Rahway, New Jersey, 1973 September 24 (Box 4)
- Mt. Ascutney Hospital and Health Center, Windsor, Vermont, 1973 September 22 (Box 4)
- Extinct Commitments, 1973 July-September (Box 4)
- Second Conference on Mononuclear Phagocytes, Leiden, The Netherlands, 1973 September 2-7 (Box 4)
- 8th Congress of the International Diabetes Federation, Bruxelles, Belgium, 1973 July 15-20 (Box 4)
- First International Symposium on Alcohol and Aldehyde Metabolizing Systems, Stockholm, Sweden, 1973 July 9-11 (Box 4)
- International Symposium on Subcellular Methodology, Guildford, Surrey, England, 1973 July 12-14 (Box 4)
- 9th International Congress of Biochemistry, Stockholm, 1973 July 1-7 (Box 4)
- International Congress of Histochemistry, Tours, France, 1973 July 1-4 (Box 4)
- Extinct Commitments, 1973 October-December (Box 5)
- Japanese-U.S. Meeting on "Protein Turnover", Stanford University, California, 1973 December 10-13 (Box 5)
- Queens College, Flushing, New York, 1973 December 7 (Box 5)
- Mount Sinai, 1973 December 6 (Box 5)
- Hoffman-La Roche, Incorporated, Nutley, New Jersey, 1973 December 5 (Box 5)
- Meeting of the Trust and Estate Gift Plans Committee, 1973 December 4 (Box 5)
- "Lysosomes ", Cell Biology in Medicine Course, Downstate Medical Center, Brooklyn, New York, 1973 November 29 (Box 5)
- 13th Annual Meeting of the American Society for Cell Biology, Miami, Florida, 1973 November 14-17 (Box 5)
- Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1973 November 16 (Box 5)
- American Health Foundation, New York, New York, 1973 November 14 (Box 5)
- Graduate Biology Group, New York University, New York, New York, 1973 November 9 (Box 5)
- Activation of Macrophanges, "Reisenburg" Castle, Ulm, Germany, 1973 October 25-26 (Box 5)
- Assemblée Générale, Association Royale des Anciens Etudiants en Brasserie de l'Université de Louvain, Heverlee, Belgium, 1973 October 21 (Box 5)
- Cérémonie Commémorative, Université de Lille, Lille, France, 1973 October 12 (Box 5)
- Extinct Commitments, 1974 January-April (Box 5)
- Sloan-Kettering Institute, Seminar, New York, New York, 1974 April 17 (Box 5)
- Visiting Scholar, Central Michigan University, Mount Pleasant, Michigan, 1974 April 26 (Box 5)
- "Subcellular Fractionation of the Aorta", Biomedical Seminar, The Rockefeller University, 1974 April 16 (Box 5)
- Seminaire, Louvain-la-Neuve, Belgium, 1974 March 15 (Box 5)
- Extinct Commitments, 1974 January-April (Box 5)
- 7th Annual Shell Lecture on Biochemistry, University of California, Davis, 1974 February 26-27 (Box 5)
- Symposium on Aging (AAAS Meeting), 1974 February 25-March 3 (Box 5)
- Interview with Shyam Dube, Mellon Foundation Applicant, 1974 February 20 (Box 5)
- Seminar, Lilly Research Laboratories, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1974 February 15 (Box 5)
- Extinct Commitments, 1974 May-September (Box 5)
- Universidad Catolica de Chile, 1974 July 6-16 (Box 5)
- Réunion du Comité Consultif de la Recherche Médicale (CCRM) de l' OMS, 1974 (Box 5)
- Conférence, "La thérapeutique lysosomotrope", Centre de Recherches de Vitry-sur-Seine, France (Rhone-Poulenc), 1974 May 28 (Box 5)
- Colloque, "Causes et Prevention des Maladies Coronaires", Fondation Cardiologique Princesse Liliane, 1974 (Box 5)
- Hungarian Academy of Sciences, Budapest, Hungary, 1974 May 20-24 (Box 5)
- Remise des Prix Académique, Académie Royale de Médicine, Bruxelles, Belgique, 1971-1973 (Box 5)
- Journee de conferences, Division de Ohimie therapeutique de la Societe Chimiqe de Belgique, 1974 May 17 (Box 5)
- Gordon Conference on Lysosomes (Box 5)
- Budget (Box 5)
- Program (Box 5)
- Correspondence, Cruickshank (Box 5)
- Applications (Box 5)
- Lysosome Club (Box 5)
- Speakers (Box 5)
- Fundraising (Box 5)
- Previous Gordon Conference (Box 5)
- Extinct Commitments, 1974 October-December (Box 5)
- Thesis Review of Francis Michael Clarke (University of Queensland), 1974 December 13 (Box 5)
- Nobel Prize Award Ceremony, Stockholm, Sweden, 1974 December 10 (Box 5)
- Seminar, Franklin McLean Memorial Research Institute and Ben May Laboratory for Cancer Research, Chicago, Illinois, 1974 November 26 (Box 5)
- Seminar, National Institutes of Health (NIH), Bethesda, Maryland, 1974 November 19 (Box 5)
- "Lysosomes", Cell Biology in Medicine Courses, Downstate Medical Center, Brooklyn, New York, 1974 November 15 (Box 5)
- Universite Rene Descartes, Paris, France, 1974 November 15 (Box 5)
- Special Tropical Diseases Programme, World Health Organization (WHO), 1974 November 12-15 (Box 5)
- Extinct Commitments, 1974 October-December (Box 5)
- "Oriented Mutations in Man", Pontifical Academy of Sciences, Rome, Italy, 1974 November 8-12 (Box 5)
- Lecture and Reception to Honor Robert W. Wissler, Cornell University Medical College, 1974 October 31 (Box 5)
- Ordres et Structurations, Réunion d' Epistémologie, Abbaye de Senanque, 1974 October 10-12 (Box 5)
- Lecture, " Therapy by way of lysosomes", Lederle Diagnostics, Pearl River, New York, 1974 October 8 (Box 5)
- Lecture, Mt. Sinai School of Medicine, New York City, 1974 October 7 (Box 5)
- Gordon Research Conferences, "Frontiers of Science", 1973 (Box 6)
- Extinct Commitments, 1975 January-February (Box 6)
- "Intralysosomal Acidity", Joint Seminar, ICP/Laboratorium vorr Biochemie, 1975 February 18 (Box 6)
- "La Révolution Biologique", Grands Conférences du Jeune Barreau, Brussels, 1975 February 17 (Box 6)
- Lecture, Belgian-American Chamber of Commerce, Pierre Hotel, New York, New York, 1975 February 13 (Box 6)
- Interview with Wiedeking, 1975 February 6 (Box 6)
- Nobel Party, Rockefeller University, 1975 February 5 (Box 6)
- Lecture, University of Miami, Miami, Florida, 1975 February 3 (Box 6)
- Cancer Planning Group, Washington University Medical School, St. Louis, Missouri, 1975 January 28 (Box 6)
- Annual Meeting of the Biochemical Society of Norway, Oslo, Norway, 1975 January 16-19 (Box 6)
- Extinct Commitments, 1975 March (Box 6)
- Doctor Honoris Causa, Rijksuniversiteit-Gent, Belgium, 1975 March 21 (Box 6)
- Visit-National Autonomous University of Mexico, Mexico City, Mexico, 1975 March 25-April 2 (Box 6)
- The Biomedical Sciences, Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation, 1975 (Box 6)
- Meeting, Max-Planck Institut fur Immunobiologie, Freiburg DDR, 1975 March 12-13 (Box 6)
- Meeting of the Advisory Board to the Max, Planck Institute for Immunobiology, 1975 March 12 (Box 6)
- Sandoz Research Institute, Symposium of Austrian Biochemical Society and the Austrian Society for Ultrastructural Research, Vienna, Austria, 1975 March 7-8 (Box 6)
- American Cancer Society, Resource Packet for 1975 Science Writers' Seminar, San Diego, California, 1975 March 21-26 (Box 6)
- American Cancer Society, 18th Science Writers' Seminar, San Diego, CA, 1975 March 21-26 (Box 6)
- Fourth Annual Workshop on the Biology of Aging, Scripps Institution of Oceanography, La Jolla (San Diego), CA, 1975 March 24-26 (Box 6)
- Extinct Commitments, 1975 April (Box 6)
- Réunion du Conseil Scientifique du Départment de Biologie Moléculaire, Rhode, St. Genèse, 1975 April 30 (Box 6)
- Societe Scientifique de Bruxelles, 1975 April 24 (Box 6)
- Déjeuner, Cercle Royal Gaulois, Brussels, 1975 April 23 (Box 6)
- "Les Membranes Biologiques et Artificielles et la Desalinisation des Eaux", Academie Potificale des Sciences, Rome, Italy, 1975 April 14-19 (Box 6)
- Remise des Prix Rene de Cooman, Mintignies-le-Tilleul, Belgium, 1975 April 11 (Box 6)
- Lecture, Lehman College, CUNY, Department of Biological Sciences, Bronx, New York, 1975 April 9 (Box 6)
- Visit by Bassleer from Université de Liège, 1975 April 8 (Box 6)
- Philadelphia, 1975 April 7-8 (Box 6)
- Reception, Belgian Consulate (820 Fifth Avenue), 1975 April 4 (Box 6)
- Extinct Commitments, 1975 May (Box 6)
- Conference on Protein Catabolism, Yugoslavia, 1975 May 25-30 (Box 6)
- Rockefeller University Council Meeting, Presentation, 1975 May 19 (Box 6)
- Lecture,Graduate Student Association, Division of Cell and Molecular Biology, State University of New York at Buffalo, 1975 May 15 (Box 6)
- Visit of the Chinese Scientists, 1975 May 9 (Box 6)
- Symposium de Biochimie et de Nutrition, Tehran, Iran, 1975 May 5-7 (Box 6)
- Troisieme Session des Journés Médicales de Bruxelles, I.C.P., 1975 May 5 (Box 6)
- Extinct, 1975, WHO (World Health Organization) Meeting, Geneva (Box 6)
- Extinct Commitments, 1975 June (Box 6)
- Ceremonie d'Hommage, U.C.L. Bruxelles, 1975 June 17 (Box 6)
- International Conference on Biological Membranes, "Membranes and Diseases", Italy, 1975 June 15-21 (Box 6)
- Lecture, Danish Biological Society, Copenhagen, Denmark, 1975 June 10 (Box 6)
- 8th Scandinavian Lipid Symposium, Helsinki, Finland, 1975 June 9 (Box 6)
- Helsinki-Copenhagen, 1975 June 6-10 (Box 6)
- 8th European Congress of Rheumatology, Helsinki, Finland, 1975 June 6 (Box 6)
- FEBS (Federation of European Biochemical Societies) Summer Course, 1975 June 2-7 (Box 6)
- Extinct Commitments, 1975 September-October (Box 7)
- WHO (World Health Organization) Meeting of the Heads of Agencies in Connection with the Special Programme for Research and Training in Tropical Diseases, Geneva, 1975 October 6-7 (Box 7)
- Research and Training in Tropical Diseases, Geneva, 1975 October 6-7 (Box 7)
- "The Future of Science", Gustavus Adolphus College, St. Peter, Minnesota, 1975 October 1-2 (Box 7)
- Lecture, "Lysosomes in Pathology and Therapeutics", University of North Dakota (Grand Forks), 1975 September 30 (Box 7)
- Directors of R. J. Reynolds, The Rockefeller University, 1975 September 9 (Box 7)
- Extinct Commitments, 1975 September-October (Box 7)
- Réunion Societé Belge de Biologie Cellulaire, Woluwé, Belgium, 1975 October 25 (Box 7)
- Amis de l'Université de Louvain, La Louviére, 1975 October 24 (Box 7)
- Journée franco-belge du cancer, Brussels, 1975 October 23 (Box 7)
- Connaissance et vie d'aujourd hui, Brussels, 1975 October 20 (Box 7)
- Association des Médicins anciens étudiants d l'UCL, Louvain, 1975 October 18 (Box 7)